var question = [
    {
        question:'Javascript is an _______ language?',
        choice1:'Object-Oriented',
        choice2:'Object-Based',
        choice3:'Procedural',
        choice4:'None of the above',
        correct: 'Object-Oriented'
    },
    {
        question:'Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?',
        choice1:'document.write()',
        choice2:'console.log()',
        choice3:'window.alert',
        choice4:'All of the above',
        correct: 'All of the above'
    },
    {
        question: 'How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?',
        choice1:'const',
        choice2:'var',
        choice3:'let',
        choice4:'constant',
        correct: 'const'
    },
    {
        question: 'When an operator’s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:',
        choice1:'Boolean',
        choice2:'Undefined',
        choice3:'Object',
        choice4:'Integer',
        correct: 'Object'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?',
        choice1:'stringify()',
        choice2:'parse()',
        choice3:'convert()',
        choice4:'None of the above',
        correct: 'stringify()'
    },
    {
        question: 'The 3 basic object attributes in Javascript are:',
        choice1:'Class, prototype, object\'s parameters',
        choice2:'Class, prototype, object\'s extensible flag',
        choice3:'Class, parameters, object\'s extensible flag',
        choice4:'Classes, Native object, and interfaces and Objext\'s extensible flag',
        correct: 'Class, prototype, object\'s extensible flag'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following are closures in Javascript?',
        choice1:'Variables',
        choice2:'Functions',
        choice3:'Objects',
        choice4:'All of the above',
        correct: 'All of the above'
    },
    {
        question: 'How to stop an interval timer in Javascript?',
        choice1:'clearInterval',
        choice2:'clearTimer',
        choice3:'intervalOver',
        choice4:'None of the above',
        correct: 'clearInterval'
    },
    {
        question: 'How do we write a comment in javascript?',
        choice1:'/* */',
        choice2:'//',
        choice3:'#',
        choice4:'$ $',
        correct: '//'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which object in Javascript doesn’t have a prototype?',
        choice1:'Base Object',
        choice2:'All objects have a prototype',
        choice3:'None of the objects have a prototype',
        choice4:'None of the above',
        correct: 'Base Object'
    }
]
